
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <channel>
   <title>cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced</title>
   <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced/</link>
   <description>Recent content on cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced</description>
   <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 19:21:51 +0200</lastBuildDate>
   
       <atom:link href="https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
   
     <item>
       <title>Course</title>
       <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced/posts/course/</link>
       <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 20:28:47 +0200</pubDate>
       
       <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced/posts/course/</guid>
       <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-course-035&#34;&gt;this course 035&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took this course out of curiosity.
I have a few years of professional experience
as a service operations engineer (or in a similar role).
So I didn&#39;t really expect to learn anything shockingly new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did, how ever, think it would be a good idea
to be at least aware on what kinds of things
are tought as &amp;ldquo;DevOps&amp;rdquo; in an academic context.
At the same time I could ensure
I had not missed anything important
while picking the basics up during work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a bonus. There is of course a credit on offer.
That does not hurt as far as I am concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do not really understand how this one question
is expected to range from 250 to 500 for a post.
Since I seem to have covered the content of the question
and am only about half way done with the word count.
I could ramble on or leave it here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
     </item>
   
     <item>
       <title>Learned</title>
       <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced/posts/learned/</link>
       <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 20:28:37 +0200</pubDate>
       
       <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-035-advanced/posts/learned/</guid>
       <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;learned-035&#34;&gt;learned 035&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I came into this course expecting to learn little.
My expectations were met.
But it is probably for the best.
My participation was doomed from the start
as far as the course staff might be concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few new things came up during the project.
Those are mainly related to the specific tooling
used for this project,
since most of them I have not used before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo seems decent enough.
Using static files,
where the use of static files
is sensible, is a great practice.
And markdown is always convenient
for simply structured text.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travis was easy enough to use.
But it did fail to wow me on any level.
Using yaml as a syntax for anything
other than loosely structured data
is always a horrible idea.
I think I will stick to Jenkins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Github pages played their own role well.
If I were hosting documentation for an open-source project
I would probably use those.
Then again, just hosting static pages is not exactly rocket science.
I would have been curious to see if there are any fancier features there.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
     </item>
   
 </channel>
</rss>
